Guide to the Hill Family Papers, 1662-1994 (bulk 1835-1970)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series VIII. Miscellaneous Materials, 1662-circa 1923
  - Certificate, James Anderson, NY State Artillery, 1845 (Box 54 (Oversize), Folder 1754)
  - Print - "Inez Milholland Boissevain, Who Died for the Freedom of Women,", circa 1923 (Box 54 (Oversize), Folder 1755)
  - Washing Irving letter, 1852; (ALS and engraving) (Box 31, Folder 1756)
  - Warrant sent to John Robinson, Lieutenant of the Tower of London, for the imprisonment of John Davies, 1662 Dec 20 (Box 31, Folder 1757)
  - Photographic print and signed note, John Tryndall, 1882 (Box 31, Folder 1758)
  - Sections of the [New York] Sun, regarding the death of President McKinley and the Moore Treaty with Colombia, 1901, 1916 (Box 54 (Oversize), Folder 1759)
  - Map of the Philippines, 1903 (Box 54 (Oversize), Folder 1760)
  - Print, "Commission Granted to Mr. Tristram Coffin, to be Chief Magistrate in and over the Islands Nantuckett and Tuckanuckett,", 1872 (Box 54 (Oversize), Folder 1761)
  - Letter, M. Ban, Second Senior Secretary of the Dept. of Education, and Chief of General Affairs, Japan. Includes engraving titled "In the Collection of Sir Thomas Hanmer Bar,", 1883 (Box 54 (Oversize), Folder 1762)
  - Land grant, Thomas Jefferson, "An Act regulating the grants of land appropriated for Military Services..." Signed by Thomas Jefferson, 1805 (Box 54 (Oversize), Folder 1763)
  - Certificate, appointment of Martin Vosburgh, Regiment of Militia in the County of Dutchess, signed by Jasper Hopper, 1798 (Box 54 (Oversize), Folder 1764)
  - "Little Eva Song - Uncle Tom's Guardian Angel,", 1852; (print on textile) (Box 54 (Oversize), Folder 1765)